

I pay great attention to code quality, software architecture, and team work. Strong analytical skills and a broad range of computer expertise that give me a good understanding and knowledge of analysis. design, coding, testing and deployment. I love new challenges and learning new skills. I consider myself an open and dynamic person. I'm always open to new opportunities and ways of expanding my knowledge. I want to be a part of the development of our future.

# Siavash Ghanbari

# **Fullstack Software Engineer**

Einbecker Str. 78 10315 Berlin

0157 345 89750

sia.gnbr@gmail.com

Website:

http://codewithsia.com

Github:

https://github.com/SiaOnbr

Stackoverflow:

https://stackoverflow.com/user s/1404642/siavash

Marital Status: Married

Date of Birth: 31.07.1988

#### Languages:

- English (Fluent)
- Persian (Native)
- German (Learning A1)

#### Education

- BSc in Software Engineering, Mazandaran University of Science and Technology, July 2012
- AD in Software Engineering, Azad University, July 2009

## **Experiences**

#### Senior Full-Stack Engineer AIMEX5

March. 2019 - Present (1 Year and 4 Months)

They are importing Luxury, high-quality products for smart homes, such as intelligent bidets, kitchen accessories etc. Aimex5 aim is to provide the best customer experience using our high-tech products. They have a product which name is Aliass, I developed an e-commerce for their product based on Reactis, Redux, Nodeis, PostgreSQL.

#### Senior Full-Stack Engineer SON Group Corporation Group

Feb. 2017 - Jan. 2020 (3 Years)

SON is a Data-Science company. We developed BI applications for The Financial Ministry of Iran, Iranian Social Affairs Organization, and some of the other important enterprise customers.

One of the fundamental steps for each BI system is collecting data. I developed an application to let users enter their financial data. This application was a spreadsheet app like Google Sheet with additional custom language that allows end-users to design their financial forms without programming knowledge. It was based on Reactis, Redux, Nodeis, and Expressis.

#### **Senior Software Engineer** Soniran Itd.

Nov. 2015 - Jan. 2017 (1 Year and 1 Month)

Soniran ltd. was a national consortium between some financial companies.

- I was responsible for developing a web application for a discounting system based on debit cards. I helped design and build new microservices and increase test coverage of existing code.
- I also developed an E-Wallet and Credit System based on each user transaction and their dashboards. (with Reactis, Redux) Notable Achievements: Reacts, Redux, Nodejs, Expressjs, Microservices, Kafka, PostgreSQL, Jest, Git, Design Patterns April 2012 - June 2015

#### **Software Engineer** Saman International Analysts

(3 Years and 4 Months) Saman Co is a Banking Solution Company. I started my professional career as a C# Developer in an agilebased team at Saman company. We developed a CORE-Banking system. Our system has been launched into 1400 branches of Keshavarzi Bank. I had worked as many different roles and worked with various technologies, during these three years, such as:

I developed an app based on ISO-8553 (Financial transaction card originated interchange messaging)

I designed and developed an automatic and manageable Updating system as an independent feature for our CORE-Banking App.

I was in charge of implementing banking logics like deposit, withdraw, transfer and etc. in our banking application.

Notable Achievements: Banking Logic, ASP.NET, WebForm, C#, Windows Services, WinForm, JavaScript, Html, CSS, JQuery, Reflection, Generics, SQL Server, DB2, PowerShell Scripting, T-SQL, OOP, Microsoft IIS, Telerik, Microsoft TFS

## Skills

- Javascript, ES6 & ES7, Typescript
- Reactis, Redux, Redux-Thunk, Nodeis, Expressis
- REST API, Web Socket, GraphQL, RabbitMQ, Kafka, OpenAPI
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- WebPack, Babel, JWT
- AWS, Lambada, Cloud9, Elastic BeansTalk, ECR, CodeCommit
- Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, PM2, Git, GitLab, Github, Eslint,
- HTML, CSS, SASS, PostCSS, Flexbox, UI/UX
- Material, Bootstrap, i18n, Lodash, Moment, Axois, HandleBars
- Enzyme, Jest, End-to-End Testing, Integration Testing, TDD
- MVC, OOP, AOP, Functional, SOLID,
- Design Patterns, Micro-service, Monolith
- · Agile, Scrum, Jira, Linux, Ubuntu

## Courses and Certificates

- Agile Development Practices | LinkedIn Learning | June 2020
- Software Architecture Foundation | LinkedIn Learning | June 2020
- Webpack for React Applications | LinkedIn Learning | June 2020
- Git: Become an Expert in Git & GitHub in 4 Hours | Udemy, February 2020
- Git Starter course, Udemy | ID: UC-597NOQ46 | June 2019
- CSS Fundamentals course, Solo-learn | ID: #1023-14416357 | June 2019
- JavaScript Tutorial course, Solo-learn | ID: #1024-14416357 | June 2019
- HTML Fundamentals course, Solo-learn | ID: #1014-14416357 | May 2019
- Microsoft ASP.NET Core, Microsoft Virtual Academy | September 2018
- Robotics Workshop, Payame Noor University | PNU / December 2011
- Future of the Robots Workshop, PNU | December 2011
- 3Ds MAX Workshop Full Course, IAU University | December 2011
- ITEX 2008, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysian Invention and Design Society | May 2008
- Advanced VB6, Technical & Vocational Training | ID: 1876068/79000092 | May 2006
- CompTIA A+, Tehran Institute of Technology | Cert-id: 112-3855 | 16104 | January 2006

## **Patents**

Intelligent Anti Earthquake Bed for Patients At hospital, Intellectual Property Organization/ REGCode: 014253 / 85a / December 2011

# **Publications**

 Modeling and simulation of traffic lights and controller unit systems by colored Petri net, Academic Journals | December 2011 | ISSN: 1992-1950 / DOI:10.5897/IJPS11.968

# **Hobbies**

Playing Guitar && Coding as Hobby && Board Games && Cooking

#### References available on request.